http://www.apparelnews.net/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy Overview
The following Privacy Policy summarizes the various ways that TLM Publishing Inc. (“Service Provider,” “we,” or “our”) treats the information you provide while using www.ApparelNews.net (“Website”). It is our goal to bring you information you need and, at the same time, protect your privacy.
Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. You can access the Privacy Policy any time by clicking on the footer on any page of the ApparelNews.net website. Your use of and/or registration on any aspect of the Website will constitute your agreement to this Privacy Policy. If you cannot agree with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Website. This Privacy Policy does not cover information collected elsewhere, including without limitation, sites linked to from the Website.
In addition to reviewing this Privacy Policy, please read our
Terms and Conditions. Your use of the Website constitutes agreement to its terms and conditions as well.
This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time; the date of the most recent revisions will appear on this page, so check back periodically. Continued access of the Website by you will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to the Privacy Policy.
The Type of Information the Website Collects
The Website generally collects personally identifying information with your specific knowledge and consent. For instance, when you enter a sweepstakes or contest, complete a survey, make a purchase, subscribe to our publication(s), or register for any portion of our services, you are asked to provide information such as your e-mail address, name, or phone number. Information such as your type of business and job function may also be requested.
Our servers may also automatically collect information about your computer when you visit the Website, including, without limitation, the type of browser software you use, the operating system you are running, the Website that referred you, and your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address. For example, we may want to know how long you spent on our site, or which pages or features you spent time with.
We will not sell, rent, swap, or authorize any third party to use your email address or any information that personally identifies you without your permission.
How the Website Uses Information Provided By You
Service Provider uses personally identifying information you supply through the Website to provide you with the service you have requested. For example, if you subscribe to any of our publications, we may use your e-mail address to send you a confirmation notice and your mailing address to send you the publication. Similarly, if you enter an online sweepstakes, we will use this information to notify you if you are a winner. We may also use the information to communicate with you about new features, products, or services, and/or to improve the services that we offer by tailoring them to your needs.
In addition, we reserve the right to use the information we collect about your computer, which may at times be able to identify you, for any lawful business purpose, including without limitation to help diagnose problems with our servers, to gather broad demographic information, and to otherwise administer our Website.
While your personally identifying information is protected as outlined above, we reserve the right to use aggregated, anonymous data about our users as a group for such business purposes as analyzing usage trends and seeking compatible advertisers and partners.
In addition, as our business changes, we may buy or sell various assets. In the event all or a portion of the assets owned or controlled by Service Provider, its parent, or any subsidiary or affiliated entity are sold, assigned, transferred, or acquired by another company, the information from and/or about our Website users may be among the transferred assets.
Cookies
“Cookies” are nuggets of information that are placed by a Website in a storage place on your own computer. We may use cookies to control the display of ads, to track usage patterns on the site, to deliver editorial content, and to record registration and personalization information. For example, if you register on any part of the Website and are given the option to save your user name and password on your computer, we can provide this convenience to you by placing a cookie on your computer.
Some of our advertisers occasionally serve you cookies as well. We do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers.
If you don‘t want any cookies, your Web browser likely includes an option that allows you to not accept them. However, if you set your browser to refuse cookies, some portions of the Website may not function properly without re-entering your name and password.
Kids & Parents
This Website is not intended for use by children, especially those under age 13. No one under age 13 is allowed to provide any personal information. Minors between the ages of 13 and 17 must get the permission of their parent(s) or legal guardian(s) before making purchases, including subscriptions, on this site.
Privacy Policy Coordinator
If you have any concerns or questions about any aspect of this policy, please feel free to contact us at California Apparel News, 110 E. Ninth St., Suite A777, Los Angeles, CA 90079
VIDEOS
Video Brought To You By Tukatech
MOST POPULAR STORIES
Planet Blue to Close Its Bricks-and-Mortar
Holiday 2020 at Citadel Outlets to Start With Christmas-Tree Lighting Nov. 14
TLM Publishing Corp.
127 E 9th Street Suite 806
Los Angeles CA 90015
213-627-3737 (P)
Contents of this site are © Copyright 2020 TLM Publishing Corp. All rights reserved.
